Hey Hollywood, thanks for taking the
time today. We'll start with John
McMullen and then we'll go to Martin
Frank.
>> Hey Hollywood, welcome to uh Philly.
First of all, um what uh what was this
process like for you and and why did you
choose the Eagles?
>> Uh thank you first off. Um the process
uh it's it's been fun. I've been
enjoying it. Um just talking to how we
talking to Nick. um just thought it
would be a good fit for me, good
opportunity, and then the culture here,
uh the team here, everything about it.
And Philly was my favorite team growing
up, so it's all it all made sense.
>> We'll go to Martin and then Dave.
>> Hey, Hollywood. Uh how's it going?
Um, I wanted to ask you about, you know,
you've obviously played with a lot of
really good quarterbacks over the years
going back to Oklahoma and obviously
Lamar and and Kyler Murray and, you
know, most recently with Mahomes. What
to you appealed about Jaylen Herz and
how do you see him in with regards to
those guys?
>> Um, man, I've been I've been watching
Jaylen play for a while. um even you
know previous teammates, everyone talked
highly about him and uh for me you know
watching watching the film on him seeing
how he's able to make stuff happen, how
composed he is um his deep ball and just
how he's able to lead uh was all
attractive to me. Um and for me, I mean
he's a Super Bowl MVP, so feel like he
stack up, you know, as a top quarterback
in this league. and I'm fortunate enough
to be here with him and the rest of the
team and um excited to come in and help.
>> We'll go to Dave and then Jeff.
>> I know you mentioned that you nearly
played with Jaylen had you gone back to
uh to school. Um did you form a
connection with him based on that um
that similarity and and have you talked
to him since you signed?
>> Uh yeah, I mean when he got to Oklahoma
we actually we hung out uh right when I
was leaving. So, you know, that was
cool. Uh, we talked since I signed. I
mean, we both excited to work with each
other. Um, and yeah, I'm I'm looking
forward to it. Hit the ground running.
>> We'll go to Jeff and then EJ.
>> Hollywood, you spoke about uh Jaylen's
deep ball. Uh, you're obviously known
for for being able to stretch defenses
and and u, you know, make plays deep.
Uh, do you still feel like, you know,
you're as explosive as when you came in
the league? And how do you think that'll
factor into what the Eagles want to do
offensively this year?
>> Uh, I feel like I'm even more explosive.
I'm excited to showcase it. Um, showcase
what I can do and uh, looking forward to
it.
>> We'll go to EJ and then Kaden.
>> Hey, Hollywood. You mentioned you were
an Eagles fan. I guess what's the
backstory there? And uh do you have many
relationships with uh people in the
building outside of of Jaylen Herz?
>> Uh yeah, like I told I remember telling
Coach Reed, my first ever memory of the
NFL was uh the Eagles and it was versus
the Patriots and from that point on I
was an Eagles fan. Um I I didn't really
remember the second part of your
question.
>> Uh just if you have any friendships with
any of the players, uh if you know many
people uh in the building already.
>> Oh yeah, I know. I know a few players
here and my boy G Cal here. Uh we came
into Oklahoma together, so I'm excited
to see him.
>> We'll go to Kaden and then Rube.
>> Welcome to to Philadelphia Hollywood. Um
at this point in your career, what's
what's your goals like as an individual?
What do you want to prove accomplish or
like maybe things you want to experience
at this stage in your career?
>> Um for me, I'm excited. I mean, I always
looking to uh prove myself, you know,
not only to, you know, my teammates, my
coaches, but to myself. I feel like I
haven't played my best ball, you know,
feel like all that is still in front of
me. So, uh, here in Philly, you know,
I'm ready to introduce Hollywood to the
to the city of Philadelphia and, uh, I'm
excited for the opportunity.
>> One real quick followup, what what is
the key to you, I guess, reaching your
potential or playing your best ball when
you maybe haven't in the past, you feel
like? Uh, I mean, you know, I got hit
with, you know, unfortunate injuries,
you know, just staying healthy, um,
staying available and the rest to take
care of it. So,
>> thank you. We'll go to Rube and then
Zach.
>> Hey, Hollywood. What was it like being
an Eagles fan in Florida? Did you walk
around with Eagles gear on and, you
know, did you kind of get some strange
looks? And did you have any favorite
players on those teams?
>> Uh, yeah, definitely. Um, a lot of my my
family it's it's all over the place with
the teams they like. But yeah, I mean my
my first memories of of Philly was with
Donovan McNab, uh, Brian Westbrook, uh,
Tio, Coach Pink, you know, he was out
there in Kansas City with me. So, uh, I
told all them guys that that it was
surreal, you know, even even being
coached by Coach Pink because I watched
him, you know, growing up.
>> We'll go to Zack and then Dave.
Okay, we'll just go to Dave here.
>> Hey, Hollywood, obviously you were a
first round pick and there are
expectations that come with that. Then
you mentioned the injuries. Uh, how do
how did you deal with that from a mental
side, not being able to maybe live up to
your potential during your career so
far?
>> Uh, I mean, I feel like everything
happens for a reason. I mean, I wouldn't
I wouldn't go back and change anything.
You know, my course is my course. My
story is my story. Uh, so I'm a eagle
and the opportunity is in front of me.
So I mean I feel like I'm right where I
need to be.
>> We'll end with Olivia here unless anyone
else has any more questions.
>> Hey Hollywood, you you mentioned that
you liked your potential fit uh with
this team as why one of the reasons why
you wanted to come here in free agency.
Um what what what exactly is that fit?
How do you envision yourself fitting
into um a new offensive scheme under a
new offensive coordinator? Uh just being
at a place like this with so many great
players with a great O line, great
defense, uh great quarterback, great
wide receivers, I I could be a weapon,
you know, I could come in and and help
out and be another asset to the team
that uh defense has got to look look out
for.
>> We'll go to Zach and then John.
>> Hey, Hollywood, can you hear me? Okay.
>> Yes, sir.
>> All right. Sorry about that.
Congratulations. Uh a a uh a two-part
question. First, how's your game evolved
over the years since you came into the
league? And then and then second, I I
know the Eagles were interested in you
uh back when you were coming out in the
draft. Did you think you'd come to
Philly earlier in your career?
>> Uh yeah, I mean, like I said before, I
wouldn't change, you know, how my career
went cuz uh having injuries helped me,
you know, evolve my game in different
areas that I probably shied away from
coming out. Uh cuz, you know, I was
always so much faster than everybody.
Um, so my game evolved so much more
that, you know, I'm so excited to
showcase what I can do and uh using all
the tools in my toolbox and uh
definitely thought I was going to be an
eagle coming out. I remember I told I
told Howie that on the phone I thought
y'all was going to draft me, but like I
said, everything happens for a reason
and uh I'm here, you know, right now in
this moment and excited for it.
>> We'll finish with John here.
>> Hey, Hollywood, you mentioned that fit.
Just curious, obviously you're busy with
your own work in Kansas City, but h how
much of a chance do you get to watch
other receivers around the league like
some uncertainty with AJ, but AJ and
Devonte specifically uh when you
envision your fit with them?
>> I watch I watch a lot of wide receiver
football. A lot of a lot of w I watch a
lot across the league. um watched a lot
of AJ, a lot of Devonte and um excited
to work with these guys and um learn
stuff from them. Hopefully they can
learn some stuff from me and uh you know
chase this ring.